Senior Web Developer (Front End)

www.nekkon.com

As confirmed by my portfolio, I combine my advanced knowledge, experience and skills with technology in order to develop professional and innovative web applications which help companies grow.

I use test-driven development principles and Agile methodologies with after-release error monitoring to produce professional and bug-free applications. I follow best practices and produce "clean code" which is comprehensive, easy to debug and maintain.

Email nekkon01@gmail.com

Phone Number

+30 6948837258



Work Experience

Senior Web Developer (Front End)

May 2017 - PRESENT, OR-CO LTD.

Developed a number of web applications used by most private and public hospitals throughout Greece. They were either rebuilt based on existing implementation (Powerbuilder) or created from scratch (using Angular and Java).

Key Responsibilities included but were not limited to:

- Supervision and management of team members on a daily basis.
- Delegating tasks and setting deadlines for internal team (trello)
- Setting up the Front-End development environment (Angular) and processes (Team of 2 Developers at beginning, with plan to add 3 more later on)
- Researching and selecting helpful Libraries and Frameworks
- Developing Components, by following modular logic and principles, which would be used by the rest of the developers throughout all apps.

Co-Developed the 3 following Web Applications.

- Admin: Admin app which manages the platform. Consists of a login view, list of apps and useful links view, management view for user roles, groups and permissions. User settings view for custom theming and user keyboard shortcuts.
- **Docman:** Document management application based on public sector requirements. Manages the process of creating documents checked and signed by a group of users. Uses Websockets to develop an instant notification system to notify changes instantly during usage. Presentation module with live presentations of the app's functionality.
- **Protocol:** Based on a previous implementation of the company. Used by the majority of the public sector in Greece. An application which manages the process of creating and validating all official Government documents. It consists of many tables, views, display of Big Data and components that could handle thousands of records in an optimized and fast way.

Used: Angular, TypeScript, Websockets, Material2, PrimeNG, CSS3, Html5

Web Developer (Front End)

July 2015 - April 2017, S2 Development LTD.

Worked in a multidisciplinary Scrum team to build a cutting edge Facebook App for Appointment Bookings. A member of a motivated team which co-operated successfully in an ambitious and innovative environment. Used Git and collaborated following continuous deployment principles and achieved:

- Lowest record of bugs in company with immediate rectification when needed. Used sentry.io for error monitoring.
- Complete training on Agile methodologies (Scrum theory and product management) by Agile Actors.
 (https://www.agileactors.com/).
- Developed a custom Registration Process which installed a Facebook app in a user's Facebook Business page (created a

Senior Web Developer (Front End)

www.nekkon.com

As confirmed by my portfolio, I combine my advanced knowledge, experience and skills with technology in order to develop professional and innovative web applications which help companies grow.

I use test-driven development principles and Agile methodologies with afterrelease error monitoring to produce professional and bug-free applications. I follow best practices and produce "clean code" which is comprehensive, easy to debug and maintain.

Email nekkon01@gmail.com

Phone Number +30 6948837258



Facebook + email login, used Graph API, Facebook and Google Analytics reporting) In this custom implementation HTML5, CSS, javascript, jQuery and bootstrap/material were used. Also migrated the custom implementation to angular2+. Rebuilt code to Typescript, HTML5, SCSS.

- Developed the Admin area of the company's site in angular2+ with Unit Tests and E2E testing. Used recurly.js and developed the front-end of credit-card and paypal payment methods.
- Developed the push script which updated production environment by using Gulp.
- Developed the Front-End for the Book'n'Bloom Facebook Application.
- All implementations used company's restful API.
- Improved efficiency of internal processes by optimizing the update script used for translated texts from 40 minutes to 4secs (100x faster) by using bulk processing and the latest libraries of MongoDB and Python
- Participated in decision making and counselling for the company's projects.

Used: javascript, jQuery, Angular, TypeScript, Facebook SDK, Google API, Gulp, RecurlyJS, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, php, python, MongoDB

Full-Stack Software Developer & Designer

JAN 2015 - JUN 2015, Freelance

Designed and Developed a web application used as a Service management tool by Media Ram. The web application included a custom dashboard and CRM.

Used: php, HTML5, CSS, javascript and jQuery (select2 and datatables).

Full-Stack Software Developer & Designer

SEP 2014 - DEC 2014, Inrealty.gr

Rebranded, Designed and Developed the website for a Real Estate agency. The website managed and displayed properties on Google maps with photos.

Used: Illustrator, Photoshop, php, mySQL, HTML5, CSS, javascript, Google Maps API and jQuery.

Full-Stack Software Developer & Designer

OCT 2010 - JUN 2013, Freelance

Developed and Designed Websites, Mobile and Desktop applications for businesses.

Used: XCode and Objective-C (iphone apps), Html, CSS and javascript (custom sites and wordpress), VB.Net (Desktop application).

Full-Stack Software Developer & Designer

SEP 2004 - AUG 2007, International Real Estate

Designed and Developed the agency's website. Designed and Developed a Property management application (with photos, database)

Used: php, mySQL, HTML and VB.NET

Senior Web Developer (Front End)

www.nekkon.com

As confirmed by my portfolio, I combine my advanced knowledge, experience and skills with technology in order to develop professional and innovative web applications which help companies grow.

I use test-driven development principles and Agile methodologies with after-release error monitoring to produce professional and bug-free applications. I follow best practices and produce "clean code" which is comprehensive, easy to debug and maintain.

Email nekkon01@gmail.com

Phone Number

+30 6948837258



Extra Activities

2017

Organised an Angular meetup group in Thessaloniki. Made various presentations about Angular and Front End Development. https://www.meetup.com/Angular-Meetup-Thessaloniki-ngThess/

Joined Toastmasters group in Thessaloniki to improve presentation and public speaking skills.

Achievements

2015 - 2017

Developed the Front End of a startup's application which resulted in to attracting one of the largest investments for Greece and in Europe (11.5 Million Euros for Book'n'Bloom).

2014

Solely Developed a web application used as a Service Management tool by Media Ram and Media Markt (one of Europe's largest retailer of consumer electronics).

2008

Presented my thesis on a new data compression algorithm in the 2nd Panhellenic Conference of Computer Science in Samos called "Eureka", which was acknowledged for its efficiency.

Education

Bachelor Degree in Applied Informatics

University of Macedonia, Greece 2002 - 2008

Diploma of Graphic Design

Swinburne University, Australia 2014

ITL Foundation (IT Service Management)

ItFutures, Australia 2012

Certificate VI in Small Business Management

RMIT University, Australia

Senior Web Developer (Front End)

www.nekkon.com

As confirmed by my portfolio, I combine my advanced knowledge, experience and skills with technology in order to develop professional and innovative web applications which help companies grow.

I use test-driven development principles and Agile methodologies with afterrelease error monitoring to produce professional and bug-free applications. I follow best practices and produce "clean code" which is comprehensive, easy to debug and maintain.

Email nekkon01@gmail.com

Phone Number

+30 6948837258



Conferences

2016

ng-europe - The Original European Angular.js Conference (Paris) DEVit - The 360° Web Development Conference (Thessaloniki)

2014

Agldeas - Design Festival (Australia, Melbourne)

2008

"Eureka" - Panhellenic Computer Science Conference (Samos)

Languages

English

Native speaker, born in Australia Certificate of Proficiency in English (Cambridge University 2008)

Greek

Native speaker

Expert In



Angular



TypeScript



jQuery



Javascript



Git



Gulp



Karma



Facebook SDK



Google API



Bootstrap



Foundation



CSS3



HTML5



PHP



MongoDB





Illustrator Photoshop